每次看到格林奇的心脏[出自影片《圣诞怪杰》]
Oh, I always tear up
涨大三倍的时候  我都止不住要流泪
When the Grinch's heart grows three sizes.
流泪是应该的
Tears seem appropriate.
心肌的扩张
Enlargement of the heart muscle,
或是肥大型心肌病  都是重病
Or hypertrophic cardiomyopathy, is a serious disease
会引起充血性心力衰竭
which could lead to congestive heart failure.
你不喜欢他是吧  谢尔顿
You really didn't like it, Sheldon?
不  正相反
No, on the contrary.
我认为格林奇是个体贴又迷人的角色
I found the Grinch to be a relatable,engaging character.
而且我十分赞赏
And I was really with him right up to the point
他屈从于社会习俗
that he succumbed to social convention
回赠礼物  拯救了圣诞节的行为
And returned the presents and saved Christmas.
多么扫兴啊
What a buzz kill that was.
我们看《圣诞雪人》的时候  他赞成出太阳
When we watch Frosty the Snowman, he roots for the sun.
请注意
Excuse me,
太阳是万物之必需
But the sun is essential for all life on Earth.
而圣诞雪人只是一个
Frosty is merely
冰雪构成的怪物  瞬息即逝  还戴着偷来的帽子
A bit of frozen supernatural ephemera in a stolen hat.
那是犯罪  而且居然从没有人为此指责他
A crime, by the way, for which he is never brought to account.
生活大爆炸第三季第十一集
我超爱装饰圣诞树
I just love decorating the Christmas tree.
感觉自己又回到了小时候
It makes me feel like a little girl again.
我小时候家里没有圣诞树
We didn't have a tree when I was growing up.
真的吗  为什么
Really? Why not?
在我家
Mmm, in my family,
节日通常是用来研究人类社会中
Holidays weren't so much celebrated as studied
它们起到的人类学和心理学意义
For their anthropological and psychological implications
而不是用来庆祝的
On human society.
真有节日气氛
Oh, sounds festive.
那你们总会互赠礼物吧
Did you at least give presents?
某种程度上
Mmm, in a way.
我们互赠研究论文
We presented papers.
然后分小组讨论  再相互评论
And then broke off into focus groups and critiqued each other.
谢尔顿  你呢
Sheldon, what about you?
你家有圣诞树吗
Did you have a Christmas tree?
当然有
Oh, yes.
有圣诞树  有马槽
We had a tree, we had a manger,
草坪上还有一个充气圣诞老人
We had an inflatable Santa Claus
身前站着一只塑料驯鹿
with plastic reindeer on the front lawn.
为了增添欢乐气氛
And to make things even more jolly,
房子的周围还有一闪一闪的灯光
there were so many blinking lights on the house
引得周围邻居纷纷来偷
They induced neighborhood-wide seizures.
所以我猜你不想帮我们装饰圣诞树咯
So I take it you don't want to help us trim the tree.
不想
I do not.
但如果你坚持
But if you insist
把一个爬满蜘蛛的的易燃物放在我家
on decorating a spider-infested fire hazard in my home
我要求你把这个加上
I would request that you add this.
那是什么
What is it?
你是在开玩笑吗
You're kidding, right?
这是牛顿爵士的半身像
It's a bust of Sir Isaac Newton.
没错  是的
Oh, sure, sure.
很有圣诞气息
Very Christmasy.
不  应该是比你挂在那棵树上的
Wait, excuse me, but it's much
其他东西都更有圣诞气息
more "Christmasy" than anything you've put on the tree.
又开始了
Here we go.
公历1642年12月25日
December 25, 1642,Julian calendar,
艾萨克·牛顿爵士诞生
Sir Isaac Newton is born.
而另一方面  耶稣其实夏天出生的
Jesus, on the other hand, was actually born in the summer
他的生日被改到了
His birthday was moved
和异教徒某个传统节日的同一天
to coincide with a traditional pagan holiday
那一天本该要点起篝火
that celebrated the winter solstice
屠宰山羊  庆祝冬至
with lit fires and slaughtered goats.
老实说
Which, frankly,
那会比和我妈妈在教堂待上12小时
sounds like more fun than 12 hours of church with my mother
然后回来吃水果蛋糕要有趣得多
followed by a fruitcake.
祝大家"牛诞快乐"
Merry Newton-mas, everyone.
虽然说不上原因  但我觉得你这祝福并不真诚
I sense that's not sincere, although I have no idea why.
没事的  牛顿爵士可以
No, it's fine. Look, Sir Issac can go
跟这个拐杖糖挂在一起
right next to this little candy cane.
不行  牛顿要放在树的顶端
No. Isaac goes at the top of the tree.
不  不行
No, he doesn't.
我明白
I understand.
你是因为牛顿声称  是他发明了微积分而抵触他
You dispute Newton's claim that he invented calculus
你想要把莱布尼茨[德数学家]挂在树顶
and you want to put Gottfried Leibniz on the top.
没错  被你发现了
Yeah, you got me.
我支持莱布尼茨
I'm a Leibniz man.
也许等你妈妈来了之后
Well, perhaps when your mother gets here,
她能启发你清醒一点
she'll talk some sense into you.
什么
What?
你妈妈要来  什么时候
Your-your mother's coming? When?
明天
Tomorrow.
那你打算什么时候告诉我
When were you going to tell me?
明天吧
Um... tomorrow?
你为什么要对我保密
Why were you keeping this a secret?
我只是  只是想
Well, I just-- I thought...
我能打断一下吗
If I can interject here,
很显然  莱纳德是担心
Obviously Leonard is concerned
怕他妈妈不会赞成你做他的伴侣
that his mother won't approve of you as his mate.
为什么她会不赞成
Why wouldn't she approve of me?
我很招人喜欢啊
I'm adorable.
你确实是  只是
You are, it's just...
我能再打断一下吗
If I can interject again.
莱纳德的家人都很优秀  成绩斐然
Leonard comes from a remarkably high-achieving family,
他们选择的伴侣也都很优秀
who have all chosen high-achieving partners.
他可能是觉得
He probably feels
他妈妈很难认同
that it's doubtful that his mother will be overly impressed
他跟一个  生平最高成就
with his dating a woman whose most significant achievement
就是背下芝士蛋糕工厂菜单的女人约会
is memorizing the Cheesecake Factory menu.
那可是份很长的菜单
Hey, it's a big menu.
光甜点就有两页
There's two pages just for desserts.
我知道
I know.
还有每天一换的当日特餐
And those specials-- they change every day.
好吧  我自己说起来就够废了
Okay, you know what? It's lame when I say it.
-你还添油加醋就更差了  -好吧
- It's just ridiculous when you pile on. - Okay.
抱歉
Sorry.
你跟她说我们在交往  她是怎么说的
So what did she say when you told her we were going out?
嗯...
Um...
你没告诉她我们在交往  是吧
You didn't tell her we were going out, did you?
嗯...
Um...
为什么不告诉她
Why not?
-嗯...  -莱纳德
- Um... - Leonard...
冥想我并不擅长
I'm no expert on meditation,
但如果你想要冷静下来
but if you're trying to calm yourself down,
我想最好说"唵"[印度教咒语]
I believe the word is "Om."
你远道来机场接我
It was so nice of you
真是太贴心了
to come all the way down to the airport to pick me up.
这没什么的
No trouble at all.
是我开的车  妈妈
I drove, Mother.
现在也是我在开
I'm driving now.
没错  宝贝  你真是妈妈的骄傲
Yes, dear. Mommy's proud.
我一直很想感谢你
I've been meaning to thank you
为我的论文加的注解
for your notes on my paper
证明了量子脑动力学理论的荒谬
disproving quantum brain dynamic theory.
我很荣幸
My pleasure.
作为非物理学家
For a non-physicist,
您对大脑水分子中的电偶极子
you have a remarkable grasp
难以形成玻色凝聚物的原因
of how electric dipoles in the brain's water molecules
理解得非常到位
could not possibly form a Bose condensate.
等等
Wait, wait, wait.
你什么时候给我妈论文加的注解
When did you send my mom notes on a paper?
8月16日
August 16.
就在她做完腕管综合症手术之后
Right after her carpal tunnel surgery.
-我谢过你送的花了吗  -谢过了
- Oh, did I thank you for the flowers? - You did.
其实我并不喜欢花
I don't really like flowers.
我也不喜欢  但那是社会习俗
Neither do I, but it's the social convention.
是啊  没错
It is, isn't it?
等等  你动过手术
Wait, wait, wait. You had surgery?
是的  谢尔顿还送了花
Yes, and Sheldon sent me flowers.
我听到了
No, I heard that.
那你还"等等"什么
Then what was all that "wait, wait, wait" about?
我只是没搞明白
I just don't understand
他怎么比我还了解你的生活
why he knows more about your life than I do.
我认为是由于我和谢尔顿
Well, I would assume it's because Sheldon
因共同的兴趣和对彼此的尊重而时常联系
and I stay in touch due to mutual interest and respect,
而你却因你那
while you avoid me,
无法释怀的童年阴影  总是躲着我
due to unresolved childhood issues.
我们认为正是这一点
It's what we think
引起了你的自恋型人格障碍
caused your narcissistic personality disorder.
我们上次视频聊天时详细地探讨了这个问题
We discussed it at length during our last video chat.
虽然不知道为什么会提到你
Although how we got onto the subject of you is baffling.
没错  既然我们又提到了
Yes, but we are on the subject,
所以我不得不问一下
so I'm obliged to ask.
莱纳德  最近过得怎样
Leonard, how are you?
挺好  妈妈  你呢
Fine, Mom. How are you?
我绝经了
Mmm, menopausal.
现在我不怎么好了
Now I'm less fine.
你弟弟订婚了  你听说了吗
Have you heard your brother has gotten engaged?
没
No.
谢尔顿  你给我讲讲吧
Sheldon, why didn't you tell me?
是我的错
My bad.
不过我代表我们两人送了礼
I did send a gift from both of us.
她是个出众的女孩子
She's a remarkable girl.
新泽西州最年轻的上诉法院法官
The youngest appeals court judge in New Jersey
还两次获得奥运会铜牌
and a two-time Olympic bronze medalist.
那你肯定非常高兴
You must be very happy.
为什么  又不是我要娶她
Why? I'm not marrying her.
你最近怎么样
So, how about you?
跟什么有趣的人在交往吗
Are you seeing anyone interesting?
我不确定她是不是有趣  不过...
Well, I'm not sure about interesting, but...
谢尔顿  还不是时候
Not the time, Sheldon.
好吧
Very well.
我们更换话题
Shall we switch topics
谈谈牛顿或莱布尼茨吧[两人曾先后独立发明微积分]
to Isaac Newton v. Gottfried Leibniz?
没事的  谢尔顿
It's all right, Sheldon.
我会假装
I will just pretend
莱纳德没叫你瞒着我
that Leonard's not withholding information.
虽然我仍要指出  莱纳德
Although, I will point out, Leonard,
我是名训练有素的精神病学家
that I am a trained psychiatrist
你现在这偷偷摸摸欲盖弥彰的举动
and you are exhibiting the same secretive behavioral tics
跟你小时候学着手淫那会没什么两样
that accompanied your learning to masturbate.
莱纳德  她太了不起了
Isn't she brilliant, Leonard?
我真羡慕你
How I envy you.
霍华德
So, Howard,
你跟拉杰  终于鼓起了勇气
have you and Rajesh finally summoned the courage
向彼此表白了你们潜在的同性恋情结吗
to express your latent homosexual feelings toward one another?
什么  没有
What? No.
为什么没有
Why not?
因为我们彼此之间  并没有
Because we don't have latent homosexual feelings
潜在的同性恋情结
toward one another.
我明白了
I see.
不  我说真的
No, really.
我现在有女朋友了
I have a girlfriend now.
那她今晚在哪呢
And where is she this evening?
她有事出了城
She had to go out of town.
她祖母去世了
Her grandmother died.
我明白了
I see.
她祖母去世了
Her grandmother died.
我说真的
Honest to God.
莱纳德  告诉她我有女朋友了
Leonard, tell her I have a girlfriend.
我不懂你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
你什么意思  不懂我在说什么
What do you mean you don't know what I'm talking about?
告诉她我有女朋友了
Tell her I have a girlfriend!
好吧
All right.
他"有女朋友了"
He "has" a "girlfriend."
她叫伯纳黛特  也在当女侍应
Her name is Bernadette. She's working as a waitress,
不过还同时上学  想成为微生物学家
but she's going to school to be a microbiologist.
霍华德  记住  你越是执着于
Howard, keep in mind that the more passionately
坚持这样的想法
you stick to this construct,
对你同伴的伤害  也就越大
the more you're hurting your partner.
你真以为对着我耳朵这么讲话有用吗
Do you really think your lips in my ear is helping?
抱歉我来晚了
Hi. Sorry I'm late.
很高兴你来了  坐
Oh, glad you're here. Uh, sit down.
我去给你拿个碟子
I'll get you a plate.
妈  记得佩妮吧
Mom, you remember Penny.
当然  那个有着无法释怀的恋父情结的
Oh, yes, the waitress slash actress
女招待兼女演员
with the unresolved father issues.
他最终正视到
Has he finally come to terms
他家的小小击球手  胸部渐隆了吗
with his little slugger growing breasts?
他送了我个足球和棒球手套做圣诞礼物
Well, he sent me a football and a catcher's mitt for Christmas,
所以我想还是没有吧
So I'm going to say no.
如果这算安慰  我们都很垂涎你的丰胸
If it helps, we're all good with your breasts.
典型的过度代偿行为
Classic overcompensation.
说到父亲  莱纳德
Oh, speaking of fathers, Leonard,
我想起来了  我和你爸离婚了
That reminds me, I'm divorcing your father.
什么
What?!
他背着我出轨
Yes. He was cheating on me.
-不是吧  -就是  和一个什么
- No!  - Yes, with some waitress
大学餐厅里的女招待
From the university cafeteria.
难以置信吧
Can you believe it?
居然和一个女招待
A waitress?
无意冒犯  亲爱的
Oh, no offense, dear.
没事  不知怎的听起来更像称赞
No, it sounded like a compliment.
什么时候的事情
When did this happen?
让我想想
Mmm, well, let's see.
谢尔顿  我什么时候和他离婚的
Sheldon, when did I leave Leonard's father?
9月22日
September 22.
对了  想起来了
Oh, yes, that's right.
就在莱纳德的狗狗死后一周
The weekend after Leonard's dog died.
米琪死了吗
Mitzy's dead?!
她已经又老又瞎了  莱纳德
She was old and blind, Leonard.
我们也无能为力
What choice did we have?
我真不敢相信
I don't believe this.
为什么我是最后一个知道的
Why am I the last to know?!
不好意思  莱纳德  离婚的是我
Excuse me, Leonard, I am the one who's getting a divorce,
死的是米琪
Mitzy is the one who is dead.
你这么大惊小怪干嘛
Why are you the one making a fuss?
好吧
You're right.
我真是抱歉
I'm-I'm-I'm-I'm sorry.
过分的是我行了吧
I'm way out of line!
佩妮  你有什么新鲜事儿吗
So, Penny, what's new in your life?
没
Nothing.
鬼都没有
Not a damn thing.
谢谢你开车送我回酒店
Thank you for driving me back to my hotel.
没事儿
Oh, it's not a problem.
我本想让莱纳德送我
I was going to ask Leonard to do it,
但他似乎有点情绪波动
But he seemed a bit emotionally unstable
这样的人可不能操纵重型机械
And you don't want someone like that operating heavy machinery.
没错  我同意
No, you do not.
你车上的"检查引擎"提示灯亮了
Your "check engine" light is on.
是啊  我真该贴张贴纸上去
Yeah, I gotta put a sticker over that.
离婚一定让你感到伤心欲绝吧
So, uh, you must be devastated about your divorce.
一点也不
Oh, not at all.
倒是坐在一辆不进行例行维护的汽车里
But I am a bit distressed to be in a vehicle
让我感到有些焦虑
That's not subjected to regular maintenance.
等等  你的婚姻终结了
Come on, I mean, you're not upset
你却一点不难过吗
that your marriage is over?
一开始  我感到类似悲伤
Well, initially I felt something akin to grief
或近似生气的情绪
And perhaps anger,
但是在那不要脸的狗杂种背叛我之后
But that's the natural reaction of the limbic system
大脑边缘系统的自然反应
To being betrayed by a loathsome son of a bitch.
很有理
Sure, sure.
但好在我已经8年没和他发生性关系了
Thankfully, my shock was somewhat mitigated by the fact
这也多少减轻了打击程度
That I haven't had intercourse with him in eight years.
居然有八年
Eight years?
这没什么
Oh, that's nothing.
自1982年来  性高潮问题都是我自行解决
I've been responsible for my own orgasms since 1982.
欧耶
Yikes.
笑什么
What's so funny?
我性高潮时都用这个词儿  "欧耶"
That's exactly what I say during orgasms: "Yikes."
我现在真想喝一杯
You know what? I could use a drink.
顺道去喝一杯吗
Do you want to stop for a drink?
-我不喝酒  -有我教你呢
- Oh, I don't drink.  - I do, I'll teach you.
莱纳德
Leonard?
Leonard...?
干嘛
What is it?
我泡了茶
I made tea.
我不想喝茶
I don't want tea.
又不是泡给你喝的
I didn't make tea for you.
这是我的茶
This is my tea.
那你告诉我干嘛
Then why are you telling me?
这算是开场白
It's a conversation starter.
这开场白烂透了
That's a lousy conversation starter.
是吗  我们不是开始聊天了吗
Oh, is it? We're conversing.
将军  你输了
Checkmate.
你到底想要干嘛  谢尔顿
What do you want, Sheldon?
我想要从企业号星舰飞船上
What I want is to be departing the starship Enterprise
乘坐单人穿梭机前往由我统治的星球
In a one-man shuttle craft headed to the planetoid I rule
著名的谢尔顿阿尔法5号星球
Known as Sheldon Alpha Five.
这我也想
I want that too.
我问你来这里干嘛
Why are you here?
当然是来安慰你
To comfort you, of course.
哦不  这个位置一点也不好
No, that's not going to work at all.
我还是到那边去安慰你吧
I'll comfort you from over here.
莱纳德  你现在的心理状态
Leonard, what you're experiencing
是典型的荣格主义危机[著名瑞士心理学家]
Is a classic Jungian crisis
个体随着年龄的增长会哀悼
In which the aging individual mourns the loss
不可能实现的理想家庭成员的缺失
Of the never-to-be realized ideal family unit.
多谢  真是倍感安慰
Thank you, that's very comforting.
我还没说到安慰部分呢
That's not the comforting part.
还没说到啊
It's not?
当然
No, no.
安慰部分是  对于你现在的感受
The comforting part is that the Germans
德国人提出了一个专业术语
Have a term for what you're feeling.
悲观主义
Weltschmerz.
意思是
It means
由假设与理想世界和现实世界之间
the depression that arises from comparing the world as it is
比较产生的落差从而导致的抑郁情绪
To a hypothetical, idealized world.
果不其然  我还真好受点了
You're right, I do feel better.
德国人在安慰方面还真有一套
Well, the Germans have always been a comforting people.
莱纳德  只要记住  即使你的亲生家人
Just remember, Leonard, where your biological family
有负于你  至少你还有我  你的替代家人
Has failed you, you always have me, your surrogate family.
你是我的替代家人
You're my surrogate family?
如果这算是安慰  我也没什么好高兴的
If it's any consolation, I'm not happy about it either.
晚安
Good night.
好了  这次来试试一口闷
Okay, now this time try drinking it all at once.
欧耶
Yikes.
自2003年起  我就自行解决酒后兴奋的问题
I've been responsible for my own buzz since 2003.
给我和我闺蜜再满上
Another round for me and my homegirl.
我感到一阵暖意扩散到四肢
I feel a spreading warmth through my extremities.
只要别暖到让你
As long as you don't feel it
想脱裤子  就准没事
Running down your pants, you're fine.
这一下太猛了
Oh, that is fascinating.
我感觉自己一下就没了矜持
I'm noticing an immediate lowering of my inhibitions.
比如说
For example,
我很认真地考虑起  去叫那打杂的
I'm seriously considering asking that busboy
让我边吃着芝士蛋糕  边在后巷强奸我
To ravish me in the alleyway while I eat cheesecake.
你怎么想
What do you think?
我们的芝士蛋糕很出名
Well, we are known for our cheesecake.
-给我们再来一杯  -对
- Hit us again.  - Yes.
如果喝一点感觉就这么爽  再喝一定更爽
If a little is good, more must be better.
-贝芙  你猜怎么着  -什么
- Hey, Bev, guess what?  - What?
我跟你儿子上床了
I'm sleeping with your son.
真的  哪个儿子
Really? Which one?
就是住在我家对面的那个
The one from whom I live across the hall... from.
那倒是很方便
Well, that's convenient.
他的小弟弟咋样
How did his penis turn out?
贝芙丽  我可不想跟我男友的母亲
Oh, Beverly, I can't talk to my boyfriend's mother
-讨论他的小弟弟  -有道理
- About his penis.  - Oh, fair enough.
那你对那打杂的
What can you tell me, if anything,
他的小弟弟  有何见解
About that busboy's penis?
其实  我只吃过芝士蛋糕
Actually, I've only had the cheesecake.
再来一杯
One more time.
莱纳德不想告诉你我俩在交往
You know, Leonard did not want to tell you we were dating.
真的
Really?
这要不就意味着
Well, that means he's either
他对你们的关系感到尴尬
Embarrassed about the relationship
要不就是他不怎么在乎他老妈
Or he doesn't care enough about his mother
不想告诉她  他在跟人交往
To tell her he's in one.
不管是哪个原因  我俩总有个人受辱
Either way, one of us should be insulted.
咱去证实下  到底是谁受辱
Well, let's go find out who.
你先去拦辆出租
You go get a taxi.
我得去往那打杂的屁股兜里
I'm gonna slip my business card
塞张我的名片
Into that busboy's back pocket,
扯起他的制服  塞他右半边屁股兜里
Cupping his firm, right buttock as I do so.
莱纳德
Leonard...?
小宝贝
Sonny boy!
快出来
Get out here!
你妈咪想跟你谈谈
Your mommy wants to talk to you!
到底怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
你麻烦大了
You're in trouble.
你干嘛不告诉我  你在追我的闺蜜
Why didn't you tell me you were tapping my homegirl?
我这样说对吗
Did I say that right?
对  不错  很不错
Yeah, not bad, not bad.
你们俩喝醉了吗
Are you guys drunk?
我倒想的
Well, I hope so.
不然  我们干嘛停在Del Taco[著名快餐店]
Otherwise, why would we have stopped at Del Taco?
你怎么能不告诉我
Now, how could you not tell me
你在跟这么个可爱迷人的姑娘
You were in a relationship
谈恋爱呢
With this lovely, charming young woman?
-多谢夸奖  -不客气
- Oh, thank you.  - You're welcome.
是因为她没啥文化
Is it because she's uneducated,
又做的是低贱的服务生吗
Trapped in a menial service position?
你不是才说我可爱又迷人吗
What the hell happened to "lovely and charming"?
你怎么能不告诉我
How come you didn't tell me
你和爸离婚了
That you and Father were getting a divorce?
怎么能不告诉我  你动过手术
How come you didn't tell me you had surgery?
怎么能不告诉我  我的狗狗死了
How come you didn't tell me my dog died?
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait...
我知道你的意思了
What I hear you saying
你是想要更亲密的母子关系
Is that you want a more intimate mother-son relationship.
是的
I do.
好了  很晚了
There. It's late.
现在  上床睡觉去
Now, go to bed.
我感到一阵暖意  扩散到心头
I'm getting a warm feeling spreading through my heart.
那是因为Del Taco[快餐店名]
That's the Del Taco.
为什么莱纳德在用他的头
Why is Leonard softly banging his head
轻撞他卧室的门
Against his bedroom door?
说起暖意  过来
Speaking of warm feelings-- come here.
还不如去吻那打杂的呢
Now I'd rather have the busboy.
谢谢你送我去机场
Thank you for taking me to the airport.
不客气
You're very welcome.
我再次重申  是我在开车
Once again, I'm driving.
而且我就在这儿呢
I'm right here.
拜托  我宿醉未醒够难受了
Please, I am very hungover
没心情照顾到你想被肯定的心情
And in no mood to satisfy your need for approval.
谢尔顿  我真心希望你能谅解
Sheldon, I do hope you'll forgive me
谅解我昨晚的不当之举
For my inappropriate behavior last night.
我并不怪你
I don't blame you.
你只是喝醉了
You were intoxicated.
谢谢
Thank you.
我怪的是佩妮
I blame Penny.
我也怪佩妮
I blame Penny, too.
佩妮真坏
Bad Penny.
等等  你们在说什么
Wait a minute, what are you talking about?
什么不当之举
What inappropriate behavior?
我想你最好不要知道
I think it's best that you not know.
-我同意  -同意
- Agreed. - Agreed.
不管了  我也同意
What the hell-- agreed.
你要好好对待这姑娘
And I want you to take very good care of this young woman.
谢谢你  贝芙丽
Oh, thank you, Beverly.
不客气
You're welcome.
她的职业前景没多大出路
She doesn't have much in the way of career prospects.
也别让她自个儿解决性高潮问题
Don't make her responsible for her own orgasms as well.
妈  记得我跟你抱怨过
Mother, remember when I was complaining
你跟我之间交流不够吗
That you don't communicate with me enough?
-记得  亲爱的  -我言过其实了
- Yes, dear.  - I'm over it.